just-drinks.com 2019-06-07

# just-drinks.com: Privacy & Cookies

* * *

Aroq Ltd has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: just-drinks.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. Log files collected by **just-drinks.com** are not shared with 3rd parties.

Where registration forms are provided, the site requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

Forms may be provided on behalf of partners when special offers or discounts on services are made available to **just-drinks.com** visitors. Information collected on these forms is not used by **just-drinks.com** for any purposes other than to provide the service in question. just-drinks.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of our web site partners.

This site also contains links to other sites. **just-drinks.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys and contests ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip/postal code, business/occupation etc.). This contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with partners and sponsors of the site at a summary level only. However, should you elect to access advertiser-provided content (including but not limited to webinars, white papers, brochures and guides) any contact information provided by you to access this content may be passed on to the advertiser concerned.

* * *

### Legitimate Interests

We process personal information for certain legitimate business purposes, which include some of the following:

  * Direct marketing: 
    * Where the processing enables us to enhance, modify personalise or otherwise improve our services/communications for the benefit of our customers
    * To provide electronic communications (emails) which we think will be of interest to you

  * Advertising: 
    * We use cookies for advertising purposes, you will have been given the option to refuse the use of cookies on your first visit to the website. See below for more details on how we use cookies on this website.

Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your personal data rights in high regard and take account of these rights.

You have the right to object to this processing if you wish, please visit the ‘Your account’ area to change your contact preferences.

* * *

### Access to your own information

At any time you may review the contact details that we hold, by signing in to ‘your account’ on our website.

To obtain a copy of any information that is not provided on our website you may send us a request to the data protection officer.

After receiving the request, we will tell you when we expect to provide you with the information, and whether we require any fee for providing it to you.

**Removal of your information**

If you wish us to remove personally identifiable information from our website, please contact the data protection officer.

This may limit the service we can provide to you.

**Verification of your information**

When we receive any request to access, edit or delete personal identifiable information we shall first take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access or otherwise taking any action. This is important to safeguard your information.

* * *

### Cookies

We use a number of different cookies on our site. If you do not know what cookies are, or how to control or delete them, then we recommend you visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/) for detailed guidance.

The list below describe the cookies we use on this site and what we use them for. Currently we operate an 'implied consent' policy which means that we assume you are happy with this usage. If you are not happy, then you should either not use this site, or you should delete the cookies having visited the site, or you should browse the site using your browser’s anonymous usage setting (called "Incognito" in Chrome, "InPrivate" for Internet Explorer, "Private Browsing" in Firefox and Safari etc.)

**First party cookies** \- These are cookies that are set by this website directly.

Type | Role | Name of Cookie(s) | Issuer(s)  
---|---|---|---  
Site Analytics Cookie | These cookies allow us to remember past visitor sessions and also to ensure visitors are automatically logged in if they so choose. | js_UniqueCookieID | just-drinks  
Site Analytics Session Cookie | These cookies allow us to understand how often users visit our site, how long they spend there, and the pages they interact with. We do not record any information that will uniquely identify you. Instead we put together the information from a very large number of users of our website to give us an overall picture of how people visit our site. This cookie will be deleted when you close your browser. | __utmc | Google Analytics  
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)  
Site Session Cookie | This is a functional cookie that helps this system to operate properly by allowing it to understand interactions in a single session. | ASP.NET_SessionId | just-drinks  
Site Analytics Persistent Cookie | These cookies allow us to understand how often users visit our site, how long they spend there, and the pages they interact with. We do not record any information that will uniquely identify you. Instead we put together the information from a very large number of users of our website to give us an overall picture of how people visit our site. | __utma   
__utmb  
__utmz | Google Analytics  
To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)  
  
**Further information on Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to collect information about visitor behaviour on our website. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on. This Analytics data is collected via a JavaScript tag in the pages of our site and is not tied to personally identifiable information. Google Analytics therefore do not collect or store your personal information (e.g. your name or address) so this information cannot be used to identify who you are. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.

You can find out more about Google’s position on privacy as regards its analytics service at [http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html](https://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

**Third party cookies**

These are cookies set on your machine by external websites whose services are used on this site. Cookies of this type are the sharing buttons across the site allow visitors to share content onto social networks. Cookies are currently set by LinkedIn, Twitter, and Facebook. In order to implement these buttons, and connect them to the relevant social networks and external sites, there are scripts from domains outside of our website. You should be aware that these sites are likely to be collecting information about what you are doing all around the internet, including on this website.

You should check the respective policies of each of these sites to see how exactly they use your information and to find out how to opt out, or delete, such information.

As you browse this site, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our partners, Facebook, Google, and Twitter, then enable us to present you with retargeting advertising on their sites and other sites based on your previous interaction with this website. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. 

You can visit [this page](https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/) to opt out of Facebook’s customised advertising, [this page](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated) to opt out of Google's customised advertising, and [this page](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20169453) to opt out of Twitter customised advertising using the ‘Do Not Track’ protocol.

**Advertising networks**

Most adverts shown on this site are hosted on Google's Doubleclick servers. The cookies set by this service are outlined here: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

We also, from time to time, accept adverts hosted by 3rd party organisations; some of these advertising services will result in a 3rd party cookie being set in order to track the viewing statistics. 

As always, remember, we only authorise our 3rd party ad servers to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. Our 3rd party ad servers do not collect, nor do we give them access, to any personally identifying information about you.

**Opting out of 3rd party cookies**

If you want to prevent a 3rd party from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each company's site and opt out. You can also select to block cookies from within your browser settings.

**Shopping cart**

We use a session cookie to remember your log-in for you and what you’ve put in the shopping basket. These we deem strictly necessary to the working of the website. If these are disabled then various functionality on the site will be broken.

* * *

### Commerce

This site provides users with opportunity to purchase research, books, training and other knowledge related items. All transactions through the just-drinks.com research store are covered by a dedicated terms and conditions statement. Visitors are encouraged to read this statement to ensure they understand the implications of using the store.

* * *

### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Data is protected both through physical means and by use of encryption and firewall technology.

Everything submitted to us is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL). This encryption method is used widely on the Internet to keep information secure. Although we use advanced encryption (Secure Socket Layers), we cannot guarantee the security of the information you transmit to us. While our site is secure, the Internet is not.

Where information is captured that may uniquely identify an individual, this information is held in an encrypted manner within our secure database.

* * *

### Choice/Opt-in and opt-out

If you would like to receive email communications from us, you need to give us your consent by double opting-in. Members can do this by visiting the 'Your Account' area on the site. 

Should you at any time wish to opt-out from receiving communications from us and our partners, you can do so at the point where we request information about you or by visiting the 'Your Account' area of the site. This site also gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service:

  1. Auto-opt-out mechanisms detailed at the base of all mailing list items
  2. Changing your communication preferences in the 'My Account' area of the site. 
  3. You can send email to Olly Wehring
  4. You can call the following telephone number: Intl +44 (0)1527 573 600 or 1-866-545-5878 Toll Free US.

* * *

### Correct/Update

Please e-mail Andrew Forth if information previously provided is believed inaccurate or incorrect. Where membership schemes exist, automatic update mechanisms are provided for self-modification of registration details.

* * *

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact:

Andrew Forth  
Chief Operations Officer  
Aroq Ltd  
Aroq House  
17A Harris Business Park  
Bromsgrove  
Worcs  
B60 4DJ
